Inventory of the Edwin Meese papers, 1941-1991
Hoover Institution Archives
- Presidential Administration of Ronald Reagan File, 1975-1991 (Boxes 554-771, 774)
  - Briefing book on the Justice Management Division (JMD), 1984 February 13 (Box-folder 685: 2)
  - Office of Legal Counsel issues briefing book, 1984 January 30 (Box-folder 685: 3)
  - Political polling flash results, Reagan/Bush December national, 1983 December 14-17 (Box-folder 685: 4)
  - Public attitudes concerning nuclear war, 1983 November 17 (Box-folder 685: 5)
  - Report on the "Transition of the President and President-Elect,", 1982 September 1 (Box-folder 685: 6)
  - Political polling flash results, 1984 June 2-5 (Box-folder 685: 7)
  - Congressional perceptions, 1984 January 27 (Box-folder 685: 8)
  - Budget, 1984 February 1 (Box-folder 685: 9)
  - Presidential characteristics, 1984 January 27 (Box-folder 685: 10)
  - Situation in Lebanon, 1984 January 30 (Box-folder 685: 11)
  - Political thermometers, 1984 January 31 (Box-folder 685: 12)
  - Political climate, 1984 February 1 (Box-folder 685: 13)
  - Presidential performance, 1984 January 31 (Box-folder 685: 14)
  - Republican National Committee
    - RNC 84-1 (January 1984)
      - Arms control, 1984 January 27 (Box-folder 686: 1)
      - Party perceptions, 1984 January 27 (Box-folder 686: 2)
      - Economic perceptions, 1984 January 27 (Box-folder 686: 3)
      - Diplomatic recognition of the Vatican, 1984 January 30 (Box-folder 686: 4)
      - Situation in El Salvador, 1984 January 31 (Box-folder 686: 5)
      - Grace Commission, 1984 January 30 (Box-folder 686: 6)
      - Job rating, crime, 1984 January 27 (Box-folder 686: 7)
    - RNC 84-3 #2622-01
      - Political polling flash results, 1984 March 7-11 (Box-folder 686: 8)
    - RNC 83-9 (August 1983)
      - Economic program, 1983 August 31 (Box-folder 686: 9)
      - Economic expectations, 1983 September 2 (Box-folder 686: 10)
      - Federal deficits, 1983 August 30 (Box-folder 686: 11)
      - Foreign policy/war and peace issues, 1983 August 29 (Box-folder 686: 12)
      - Nuclear weapons freeze, 1983 August 31 (Box-folder 686: 13)
      - El Salvador, 1983 August 31 (Box-folder 686: 14)
      - Presidential performance, 1983 August 30 (Box-folder 686: 15)
      - Education, 1983 August 29 (Box-folder 686: 16)
      - More power to the states, 1983 August 31 (Box-folder 686: 17)
      - Congressional perceptions, 1983 September 2 (Box-folder 686: 18)
      - Political thermometers, 1983 September 2 (Box-folder 686: 19)
      - Political climate, 1983 August 29 (Box-folder 686: 20)
      - Perceptions of the president, 1983 August 26 (Box-folder 686: 21)
      - Campaign promises, 1983 August 26 (Box-folder 686: 22)
      - "Homosexuality: An Alternative Lifestyle,", 1983 August 31 (Box-folder 686: 23)
    - National attitudes concerning crime and the judicial system in America, 1984 January 19 (Box-folder 686: 24)
    - Political polling flash results national tracking, Reagan-Bush '84, 1984 September 12-18 (Box-folder 686: 25)
    - QUBE results on "The Day After,", 1983 November 28 (Box-folder 686: 26)
    - Issues from the national survey, 1981 May 29 (Box-folder 686: 27)
    - RNC 83-12 (November 1983)
      - Defense spending, 1983 December 12 (Box-folder 687: 1)
      - Social programs spending preferences, 1983 December 13 (Box-folder 687: 2)
      - Perceptions of the president, 1983 December 8 (Box-folder 687: 3)
      - Environment, 1983 December 12 (Box-folder 687: 4)
      - Economic perceptions, 1983 December 9 (Box-folder 687: 5)
      - Political climate, 1983 December 15 (Box-folder 687: 6)
      - School prayer vote, 1983 December 9 (Box-folder 687: 7)
      - Civil rights, 1983 December 12 (Box-folder 687: 8)
      - Presidential performance, 1983 December 12 (Box-folder 687: 9)
      - Education, 1983 December 12 (Box-folder 687: 10)
      - Crime, 1983 December 9 (Box-folder 687: 11)
      - Political thermometers, 1983 December 9 (Box-folder 687: 12)
      - Situation in Lebanon, 1983 December 2 (Box-folder 687: 13)
      - Equal Rights Amendment, 1983 December 9 (Box-folder 687: 14)
      - Partisanship, 1983 December 9 (Box-folder 687: 15)
      - Economic expectations, 1983 December 8 (Box-folder 687: 16)
      - Congressional perceptions, 1983 December 8 (Box-folder 687: 17)
      - Diplomatic recognition of the Vatican, 1983 December 12 (Box-folder 687: 18)
      - Thermometer ratings of Cabinet members and others, 1983 December 13 (Box-folder 687: 19)
      - Drug usage, 1983 December 12 (Box-folder 687: 20)
      - Jerry Falwell, 1983 December 20 (Box-folder 687: 21)
      - Grenada, 1983 December 12 (Box-folder 687: 22)
      - Arms control and nuclear war, 1983 December 12 (Box-folder 687: 23)
    - Briefing materials, D. Lowell Jensen, 1984 February 3 (Box-folder 687: 24)
    - Data extracted from Decision Making Information's survey data bank on civil rights/privacy, 1984 February 15 (Box-folder 687: 25)
    - Political polling flash results, 1983 June 25-27 (Box-folder 687: 26)
    - RNC 11 (October 18-21, 1983)
      - Perceptions of the president, 1983 November 9 (Box-folder 687: 27)
      - Presidential speech, 1983 November 9 (Box-folder 687: 28)
    - RNC 83-BRUSHFIRE (October 26-28, 1983)
      - Grenada, 1983 November 9 (Box-folder 687: 29)
      - Presidential speech, 1983 November 9 (Box-folder 687: 30)
    - RNC 11 (October 18-21, 1983)
      - Thermometer ratings of White House and Cabinet members, 1983 November 7 (Box-folder 687: 31)
      - Economic expectations, 1983 November 10 (Box-folder 687: 32)
      - Congressional perceptions, 1983 November 7 (Box-folder 687: 33)
      - Government waste and fraud, 1983 November 7 (Box-folder 687: 34)
    - RNC 83-BRUSHFIRE (October 26-28, 1983)
      - Presidential performance, 1983 November 9 (Box-folder 687: 35)
      - Lebanon, 1983 November 9 (Box-folder 688: 1)
      - Soviet military threat, 1983 November 9 (Box-folder 688: 2)
    - RNC 11 (October 18-21, 1983)
      - Arms control, 1983 November 7 (Box-folder 688: 3)
      - Partisanship, 1983 November 7 (Box-folder 688: 4)
      - Political thermometers, 1983 November 7 (Box-folder 688: 5)
      - Education, 1983 November 7 (Box-folder 688: 6)
    - RNC 83-BRUSHFIRE (October 26-28, 1983)
      - Political climate, 1983 November 10 (Box-folder 688: 7)
      - Acid rain, 1983 November 9 (Box-folder 688: 8)
    - Political polling flash results, RNC83-12 #2301-01, 1983 November 25-29 (Box-folder 688: 9)
    - Presidential ratings, 1983 July 8 (Box-folder 688: 10)
    - Harris Survey, "If Guilty of Improper Acts, Reagan Aides Should Be Fired,", 1983 July 28 (Box-folder 688: 11)
    - Korean airliner incident, 1983 September 21 (Box-folder 688: 12)
    - Situation in Lebanon, 1983 September 21 (Box-folder 688: 13)
    - "Public Attitudes on New Federalism: The Role of Federal, State and Local Government,", 1983 December 8 (Box-folder 688: 14)
    - "Public Attitudes on Tuition Tax Credits,", 1983 December 8 (Box-folder 688: 15)
    - Harris Survey, "Should Reagan Seek Re-Election,", 1984 January 5 (Box-folder 688: 16)
    - Summary of MOR January Mississippi study, Reagan and Mondale voting, 1984 January 17 (Box-folder 688: 17)
    - Commission on Hunger, 1984 January 30 (Box-folder 688: 18)
    - Importance of family values in society, RNC84-1, 1984 January 30 (Box-folder 688: 19)
    - National tracking update, 1984 September 19-23 (Box-folder 688: 20)
    - Political polling flash results, national tracking, Reagan-Bush '84, 1984 September 19-25 (Box-folder 688: 21)
    - Political polling flash results, national tracking, Reagan-Bush '84, 1984 October 17 (Box-folder 688: 22)
    - "A Statewide Survey of Republican Primary Voters in Florida for Reagan for President,", 1979 November-December (Box-folder 688: 23-24)
    - "A National Brushfire Survey of Voter Attitudes Prepared for the Republican National Committee,", 1982 July (Box-folder 689: 1)
    - "A National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle VII for the Republican National Committee," Volume 1 of 3, 1981 May (Box-folder 689: 2)
    - Selection of a vice president, 1980 June 25 (Box-folder 689: 3)
    - RNC 83-9 (August 17-22, 1983)
      - Equal Rights Amendment, 1983 August 30 (Box-folder 689: 4)
      - Civil rights, 1983 August 29 (Box-folder 689: 5)
    - "A Statewide Survey of Republican Primary Voters in Vermont for Reagan for President,", 1979 November-December (Box-folder 689: 6)
    - Voter attitudes toward vice presidential attributes and potential nominees for The Reagan for President Committee, 1980 June (Box-folder 689: 7)
    - Table of contents, budget outlook, 1982 (Box-folder 689: 8)
    - Decision Making Information booklet, undated (Box-folder 689: 9)
  - Confirmation correspondence, 1985
    - A-H (Box-folder 690: 1-4)
    - I-V (Box-folder 691: 1-6)
    - W-Z (Box-folder 692: 1-2)
  - Domestic Policy Council, 1988 (Box-folder 692: 3)
  - Washington Wire, "A Special Weekly Report From The Wall Street Journal's Capital Bureau,", 1985 November 1 (Box-folder 692: 4)
  - Decision Making Information, 1983 October (Box-folder 692: 5)
  - Judge O'Connor confirmation, 1967-1981 (Box-folder 692: 6-10)
  - Judge O'Connor confirmation (cont'd.), 1967-1981 (Box-folder 693: 1-2)
  - Alphabetical file
    - A, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 693: 3)
    - Allin, Mort, 1981 (Box-folder 693: 4)
    - American Business Conference, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 693: 5)
    - Anderson, Martin, 1984 (Box-folder 693: 6)
    - B, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 693: 7)
    - Baker, James, 1981 (Box-folder 693: 8)
    - Bannister, Robert D., National Association of Home Builders, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 693: 9)
    - Beal, Richard, 1981 (Box-folder 693: 10)
    - Beckner, John, 1982 (Box-folder 693: 11)
    - Bendetsen, Karl, American Security Council, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 693: 12)
    - Bennett, Jack, 1984 (Box-folder 694: 1)
    - Bergstrom, Lutheran Church, 1981 (Box-folder 694: 2)
    - Bolger, William, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 694: 3)
    - Boltz, Carol J., Dean Witter Reynolds, Inc., undated (Box-folder 694: 4)
    - Bond, Kit, 1981 (Box-folder 694: 5)
    - Bradley, Mel, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 694: 6)
    - Brady, Jim, 1981 (Box-folder 694: 7)
    - Brewer, Roy, 1984 (Box-folder 694: 8)
    - Brown, Clarence, 1985 (Box-folder 694: 9)
    - Brown, Edmund G., 1981-1982 (Box-folder 694: 10)
    - Burns, Arthur, 1982 (Box-folder 694: 11)
    - Bush, George, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 694: 12)
    - Byers, Buckley M., 1982 (Box-folder 694: 13)
    - C, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 694: 14)
    - California Lutheran College, 1984 (Box-folder 694: 15)
    - Carleson, Bob, 1981 (Box-folder 694: 16)
    - Carrington, Frank, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 694: 17)
    - Chapman, Bruce, memoranda, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 694: 18)
    - Chennault, Anna, 1981 (Box-folder 694: 19)
    - Clifford, Clark, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 694: 20)
    - Codus, William R., 1982 (Box-folder 694: 21)
    - Coles, James B., 1984 (Box-folder 694: 22)
    - Conger, Clement, 1981 (Box-folder 694: 23)
    - Cooke, Jack Kent, 1984 (Box-folder 694: 24)
    - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1982 (Box-folder 694: 25)
    - Coyne, Marshall, 1984 (Box-folder 694: 26)
    - Cribb, Kenneth, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 694: 27)
    - Curran, Gary, 1984 (Box-folder 694: 28)
    - Curry, Jerry M. G., 1984 (Box-folder 694: 29)
    - D, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 694: 30)
    - Darman, Richard, 1981 (Box-folder 694: 31)
    - Dolan, Doris, 1984 (Box-folder 695: 1)
    - Dole, Elizabeth, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 695: 2)
    - Dozier, Gilbert L., petition for executive clemency, 1984 (Box-folder 695: 3)
    - E, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 695: 4)
    - Ellingwood, Herb, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 695: 5-7)
    - Entin, Stephen Jay, 1980 (Box-folder 695: 8)
    - Erthein, John S., 1981-1982 (Box-folder 695: 9)
    - F, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 695: 10)
    - Federal Managers' Association, 1982 (Box-folder 696: 1)
    - Feeny, Sandra D., 1982 (Box-folder 696: 2)
    - Factor, Mallory, 1984 (Box-folder 696: 3)
    - Feith, Doug, 1982 (Box-folder 696: 4)
    - Feldman, Trudie, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 696: 5)
    - Feldstein, Martin, 1984 (Box-folder 696: 6)
    - Feulner, Edwin, 1982 (Box-folder 696: 7)
    - Fielding, Fred, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 696: 8-9)
    - Fike, Edward L., undated (Box-folder 696: 10)
    - L.W. (Bill) Lane, Lane Publishing Company, 1984 (Box-folder 696: 11)
    - Filante, William J., 1982 (Box-folder 696: 12)
    - Flaum, Joel, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 696: 13)
    - Flynt, Larry, 1984 (Box-folder 696: 14)
    - Frankum, Ron, 1981 (Box-folder 696: 15)
    - Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 696: 16)
    - Freedoms Foundation, Robert Miller, 1984 (Box-folder 696: 17)
    - G, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 696: 18)
    - Gergen, David, 1981 (Box-folder 696: 19)
    - Gnau, John, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 696: 20)
    - Gruver, Bill, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 696: 21)
    - H, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 696: 22)
    - Habib, Philip, 1981 (Box-folder 696: 23)
    - Haggedorn, Tom, 1983 (Box-folder 696: 24)
    - Haggerty, Thomas J., 1984 (Box-folder 696: 25)
    - Hammer, Armand, 1981 (Box-folder 696: 26)
    - Hannaford, Peter, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 696: 27)
    - Harper, Ed, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 697: 1)
    - Hekman, John, 1982 (Box-folder 697: 2)
    - Helms, Jesse, 1981 (Box-folder 697: 3)
    - Hickey, Ed, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 697: 4)
    - Hinckley, John, 1982 (Box-folder 697: 5)
    - Holmes, Joseph, 1981 (Box-folder 697: 6)
    - Holtzman, Marc, 1981 (Box-folder 697: 7)
    - Hoxie, Gordon, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 697: 8-9)
    - Hoover Institution, 1984 (Box-folder 697: 10)
    - Hugel, Max, 1984 (Box-folder 697: 11)
    - I, 1985 (Box-folder 697: 12)
    - International Association of Chiefs of Police (IACP), 1982 (Box-folder 697: 13)
    - J, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 697: 14)
    - Jensen, Lowell, 1981 (Box-folder 697: 15)
    - Junior Statesmen Foundation, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 697: 16)
    - Kemp, Jack, 1981 (Box-folder 697: 17)
    - Kersey, Walter George, 1984 (Box-folder 697: 18)
    - Keyworth, George A., 1981-1984 (Box-folder 697: 19)
    - Kennedy, William, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 697: 20)
    - Kerchum, Ralph, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 697: 21)
    - King, Edward J., 1980 (Box-folder 698: 1)
    - Kingon, Al, 1982 (Box-folder 698: 2)
    - Knause, Mark, undated (Box-folder 698: 3)
    - L, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 698: 4)
    - Laxalt, Paul, 1981 (Box-folder 698: 5)
    - Lehrman, Lewis, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 698: 6)
    - Lindsey, Bruce, 1981 (Box-folder 698: 7)
    - Lodwick, Seeley G., 1983 (Box-folder 698: 8)
    - M, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 698: 9)
    - Master calendar of admin speakers, 1984 (Box-folder 698: 10)
    - Malone, James M., 1982 (Box-folder 698: 11)
    - Margolis, Lawrence S., 1981 (Box-folder 698: 12)
    - Marquez, Alfred, 1983 (Box-folder 698: 13)
    - Martin, Preston, 1982 (Box-folder 698: 14)
    - Meese, Edwin, confirmation-related materials, 1984 (Box-folder 698: 15)
    - Meese, Edwin, personal, 1984 (Box-folder 698: 16)
    - Melady, Thomas Patrick, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 698: 17)
    - Minor, Ernie, 1981 (Box-folder 698: 18)
    - Morris, Annette, 1984 (Box-folder 698: 19)
    - Murphy, Betty, 1982 (Box-folder 698: 20)
    - McClaughry, John, 1981 (Box-folder 698: 21)
    - McKinnon, Dan, 1981 (Box-folder 698: 22)
    - N, 1984 (Box-folder 698: 23)
    - Nollinger, Mark, 1984 (Box-folder 698: 24)
    - O, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 698: 25)
    - Oliver, Daniel, 1984 (Box-folder 698: 26)
    - P, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 698: 27)
    - Pappas, Frank, 1981 (Box-folder 699: 1)
    - Patrick, Carol, 1981 (Box-folder 699: 2)
    - Payne, Thomas, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 3)
    - Peace Corps, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 4)
    - Pond, Judy, 1981 (Box-folder 699: 5)
    - Poole, Bill, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 6)
    - Pope John Paul II, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 699: 7)
    - Porter, Roger, 1984 (Box-folder 699: 8)
    - Presser, Jackie, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 9)
  - Alphabetical file
    - Agency for International Development, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 10)
    - Berkeley, Brandon Moore, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 11)
    - Clohan, William, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 12)
    - Cohn, Alvin W., 1982 (Box-folder 699: 13)
    - Crosse, St. George IB, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 14)
    - Cryer, William, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 15)
    - Derwinski, Ed, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 16)
    - Ambassadorial appointments, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 17)
    - Douglas, Charles G., 1981 (Box-folder 699: 18)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC) Reagan appointments, 1983 (Box-folder 699: 19)
    - Federal Communications Commission, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 20)
    - Federal Trade Commission, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 21)
    - Housing and Urban Development (HUD), 1981-1982 (Box-folder 699: 22)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 23)
    - Justice, Department of, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 24)
    - Kozinski, Alex, 1981 (Box-folder 699: 25)
  - Alphabetical file
    - R, 1984 (Box-folder 699: 26)
    - Legal Services Corporation, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 27)
    - Reynolds, Nancy Clark, 1981 (Box-folder 699: 28)
    - Roberts, Norman, 1981 (Box-folder 699: 29)
    - Rogers, John F. W., 1981 (Box-folder 699: 30)
    - Rowny, Edward, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 699: 31)
    - Ryskind, Alan, undated (Box-folder 699: 32)
      Interview of Meese.
    - S, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 699: 33)
    - Santarelli, Donald, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 699: 34)
    - Schabarum, Peter F., 1981 (Box-folder 699: 35)
    - Schwartz, Michael, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 36)
    - Shakespeare, Frank, 1981 (Box-folder 699: 37)
    - Shine, Henry, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 38)
    - Silberman, Laurence H., 1979 (Box-folder 699: 39)
    - Slipyj, Josyf Cardinal, 1984 (Box-folder 699: 40)
    - Small, Karna, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 41)
    - Sonnenberg, Maurice, 1981 (Box-folder 699: 42)
    - Stans, Maurice, 1982 (Box-folder 699: 43)
    - Sousa, Anthony G., undated (Box-folder 700: 1)
    - Stein, Jacob, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 700: 2)
    - Stockman, David, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 700: 3)
    - Stone, W. Clement, 1981 (Box-folder 700: 4)
    - Svahn, Jack, undated (Box-folder 700: 5)
    - T, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 700: 6)
    - Takamine, Joe, 1981 (Box-folder 700: 7)
    - Tambs, Lewis A., 1982 (Box-folder 700: 8)
    - Tanter, Raymond, 1982 (Box-folder 700: 9)
    - Thurmond, Strom, 1985 (Box-folder 700: 10)
    - Timmons, William, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 700: 11)
    - Toledano, Ben C., 1983 (Box-folder 700: 12)
    - Turnage, Thomas, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 700: 13)
    - Tower, John, 1981 (Box-folder 700: 14)
    - Tyson, Chuck, 1981 (Box-folder 700: 15)
    - V, 1985 (Box-folder 700: 16)
    - Veterans Administration, 1982 (Box-folder 700: 17)
    - Van Cleave, William, 1981 (Box-folder 700: 18)
    - Vessey, John W., 1984 (Box-folder 700: 19)
    - Vieth, Harvey, 1982 (Box-folder 700: 20)
    - W, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 700: 21)
    - Webb, William Arthur, 1982 (Box-folder 700: 22)
    - Weidenbaum, Murray, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 700: 23)
    - Wheeler, John, III, 1981 (Box-folder 700: 24)
    - White, Stan, 1982 (Box-folder 700: 25)
    - Wilson, William A., 1981 (Box-folder 700: 26)
    - Will, George, 1981 (Box-folder 700: 27)
    - Williams, Spencer, 1981 (Box-folder 700: 28)
    - Williamson, Richard, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 700: 29)
    - Wirthlin, Richard, 1981 (Box-folder 701: 1)
    - Woodson, Bob, 1982 (Box-folder 701: 2)
    - Wright, Joe, 1984 (Box-folder 701: 3)
    - Wyatt, O.S., Jr., 1981 (Box-folder 701: 4)
    - Yerby, George P., 1982 (Box-folder 701: 5)
    - Zable, Walt, 1984 (Box-folder 701: 6)
    - Zacks, Gordon, 1981 (Box-folder 701: 7)
  - "The White House Magazine Summary: A Weekly Review of Leading U.S. Magazines,", 1983 October-November (Box-folder 701: 8)
  - Press briefing by Larry Speakes, 1984 March-April (Box-folder 701: 9)
  - "Under Fire," Newsweek, 1984 (Box-folder 701: 10)
  - "Over His Head-Why Ed Meese Has Failed in Washington," San Jose Mercury News, 1984 March (Box-folder 701: 11)
  - "On the Right" by William F. Buckley Jr., 1984 (Box-folder 701: 12)
  - "White House News Summary Special Edition,", 1983 October - 1984 April (Box-folder 701: 13)
  - "The White House News Summary,", 1983 August, 1984 March (Box-folder 701: 14)
  - Articles, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 701: 15)
  - Articles (cont'd.), 1983-1984 (Box-folder 702: 1-3)
  - Platform meeting, 1984 May (Box-folder 702: 4)
  - Political elections and debates, 1984 (Box-folder 702: 5)
  - Political elections and debates (cont'd.), 1984 (Box-folder 703: 1-5)
  - U.S. Department of Justice, 1985 (Box-folder 704: 1)
  - Remarks of the attorney general to the International Association of Chiefs of Police, Houston, Texas, 1985 October 15 (Box-folder 704: 2)
  - Seventh German-American Roundtable, 1985 (Box-folder 704: 3)
  - Statement of Dr. Janet L. Norwood before the Joint Economic Committee, 1985 (Box-folder 704: 4)
  - Bulletin of the Federal Courts, 1984 January-December (Box-folder 704: 5)
  - U.S. goals for the new trade round, 1985 (Box-folder 704: 6)
  - "Nicaragua, The Stolen Revolution," by Ambassador J. William Middendorf, II, 1985 (Box-folder 704: 7)
  - President's proposed public and private partnership for public safety, 1985 (Box-folder 704: 8)
  - Notes from meeting with Colombian President Belisario Betancur, 1985 (Box-folder 704: 9)
  - Selection of archivist of the United States, 1985 (Box-folder 704: 10)
  - Grove City, civil rights legislation, 1985 (Box-folder 704: 11)
  - Jonathan Moore, 1985 (Box-folder 704: 12)
  - Ticor case and independent agencies, 1985 (Box-folder 704: 13)
  - Ninety-ninth Congress First Session S. 704, 1985 (Box-folder 704: 14)
  - Talking points on 1986 appropriation bill (Box-folder 704: 15)
  - Operation Delta-9, 1985 August (Box-folder 704: 16)
  - Draft of the International Association of Chiefs of Police (IACP) meeting, 1985 October (Box-folder 704: 17)
  - Hijacking of Italian cruise ship and potential United States prosecution, 1985 October (Box-folder 704: 18)
  - Campaign Against Marijuana Planting (CAMP), 1985 (Box-folder 704: 19)
  - Meeting with Al Kingon, 1985 November (Box-folder 704: 20)
  - Affirmative action, undated (Box-folder 704: 21)
  - Clippings, 1985 (Box-folder 704: 22)
  - Memorandum from the White House, 1985 April (Box-folder 704: 23)
  - Miscellaneous written notes, 1985 October (Box-folder 704: 24)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box-folder 704: 25)
  - Drug enforcement report, undated (Box-folder 704: 26)
  - State Medicaid fraud control units, 1985 (Box-folder 704: 27)
  - "Economic Issues Recede as the Most Pressing Problems Facing the Public in Their Communities and the State" by Mervin Field, 1985 (Box-folder 704: 28)
  - Correspondence to Reagan from Thomas Iskrzycki, 1985 February (Box-folder 704: 29)
  - Domestic Policy Council, microfilm inventory, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 705: 1)
    See also: box 455 for microfilm reels.
  - Procuraduria General de la Republica, Direccion de Participacion Social, Programa ADEFAR, undated (Box-folder 705: 2)
  - Notebook of Q and A's for the presidential debate, 1984 October (Box-folder 705: 3)
  - Presidential debates, 1984 (Box-folder 705: 4)
  - Domestic Policy Council (DPC) XIX, 1988 July-August (Box-folder 705: 5-6)
  - Briefing information about community relations service, 1984 (Box-folder 706: 1)
  - Criminal Division, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 706: 2)
  - Labor and Natural Resources, division briefing book, 1984 February (Box-folder 706: 3)
  - Speeches and travel file
    - New York speech to Economic Club of New York, 1986 January (Box-folder 706: 4)
    - Williamsburg Conference on Federalism, 1986 January 24-26 (Box-folder 706: 5)
    - Baltimore, Maryland, midyear meetings of Conference of Chief Judges, 1986 February (Box-folder 706: 6)